https://www.glknife.com/contact-us/privacy-policy-copyright-usage-agreement/

MenuHomeProductsDicer & Dicer Bed KnivesExtrusion DiesFeed Rolls / Pull RollsGranulator Knives / Granulator ScreensHardened & Ground Machine WaysHelical Pelletizer RotorsMachine Knives / Misc. & Special OrderMulti-Groove Bottom BandsPaper Trimmer Knives / Cutting SticksPelletizer KnivesPerforator KnivesPneumatic Air Knife HoldersPneumatic Air Trim In-Line Chopper KnivesPulverizer Discs / Pulverizer PlatesRazor BladesScore KnivesScraper KnivesShear Blades and Rotary ShearsSheeter Knives / Pulp Cutter KnivesSlitter Anvils / RollsSlitter KnivesSlitter Sleeves / ShaftsTooth Cut Off Knives / Packaging KnivesUnderwater Melt Cutter Die / Face ResurfacingWork Rest / Centerless Grinder / Guides & Cams CloseIndustriesConverting, Labeling, & Pressure SensitiveFood ProcessingMetal WorkingPackagingPlastics Compounding / RecyclingPrinting & BookbindingPulp & PaperRubberSpecial Purpose / Custom ToolingWoodworking CloseTechnologyServicesMetallurgyCarbon Alloy Tool SteelsCobalt Alloy Tool Steels – Stellite®Composite Inlaid Tool SteelsHigh Performance Stainless SteelsHigh Speed Tool SteelsICE™ Inlaid CarbidePowdered MetallurgyTitanium Carbide (TiC) Ferro-Tic®Tungsten Carbide (Wc)Zirconia Ceramics CloseContact UsWho We AreCustomer ServicePrivacy Policy / Copyright / Usage AgreementRequest a Quote Close
Close
Privacy Policy / Copyright / Usage Agreement //
Copyright
The content of this Web site (graphics, text and any and all other elements) is © Copyright 2003 by Great Lakes Industrial Knife and may not be reprinted or retransmitted in whole or part without expressed written consent of Great Lakes Industrial Knife.
2003, Great Lakes Industrial Knife. all rights reserved
The Great Lakes Industrial Knife Privacy Policy Agreement
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy, which explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable data may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include:
Name
Address
E-mail address
Survey questions
Phone number
How We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We may use your e-mail address to communicate with you, for example, to notify you of special offers or products you might find of interest. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. We may also use these e-mail addresses to provide order status and order tracking information, and to respond to queries.
We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and share with our advertising agencies. For example, we may tell an advertising agency that x number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that y number of men and z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to personally identify those individuals. If you choose to register or receive products or materials from us, or to otherwise give us personal information, we may store some or all of that personal information and use it for marketing research and marketing purposes, which may include sharing it with dealerships or with various suppliers that provide marketing, research, or other services for us.
We will never sell your personal information to any other company.
2003, Great Lakes Industrial Knife all rights reserved
Finally, we never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
A Word On “Cookies”
“Cookies” are small items of data that some websites either write to your hard drive upon your visit to their site(s) or store in the browser. These data files contain information the site can use to organize the pages you have visited on a particular website. Some of our websites may use “cookie” technology to measure site activity and tailor information to fit your personal interests. In this way, we can deliver tailor-made information suiting your personal interests upon your next visit to our site(s). Our use of “cookies” technology is, thus, to provide you with a more individualized delivery of information and an optimal viewing experience.
Our Commitment To Data Security
Because your privacy is important to us, we have installed safeguards to secure the credit card information we collect online. Our e-commerce site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology supported by Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator/Communicator, and other popular browsers to protect your online transactions. SSL encrypts your credit card number, name, address, and phone number before they travel over the Internet. We also use additional technologies and measures to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure appropriate use of this information.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please e-mail us at:
sales@glknife.com
Great Lakes Industrial Knife Usage Agreement
Initial Notice
Thank you for visiting The Great Lakes Industrial Knife Web site. Please read carefully the following legal agreement before using this Web site. By using this Web site, you signify your assent to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please disconnect from and do not use this Web site.
List Of Restrictions
Neither the Web site nor any element thereof, including, without limitation, text, graphics, images, or other materials, may be copied, repurposed, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or redistributed, except that you may download one copy of such materials to your individual computer solely for your personal, non-commercial use only (which also excludes any use by any governmental, educational, charitable, or other institutional use that is not strictly a personal use by you), provided that all copyright and other proprietary notices appearing on such materials are strictly preserved without any alteration, modification, or obfuscation. With respect to any software downloaded by you from the Web site, such software, and all elements thereof, are licensed to you by Great Lakes Industrial Knife for your personal use only. You may not modify or prepare derivative works based upon the Web site, or any element thereof, and you may not redistribute, sell, recompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, or otherwise attempt to access the source code to any software downloaded from the Web site.
Reservation Of Rights
All rights, titles, and interests in and to this Web site are owned by Great Lakes Industrial Knife. The Web site is protected by United States copyright law and international treaty provisions, including, without limitation, the Berne Convention. The Great Lakes Industrial Knife logo, the word “I.C.E.™”, are registered trademarks of Great Lakes Industrial Knife. No trademarks or service marks owned by Great Lakes Industrial Knife may be used without the express written consent of Great Lakes Industrial Knife all rights not expressly licensed hereunder are reserved by Great Lakes Industrial Knife. Great Lakes Industrial Knife reserves all rights not expressly licensed hereunder.
2003, Great Lakes Industrial Knife all rights reserved
Translate »
